In a Few Hours He'll Either be an Assassin, Hero, or Dead.
Perfect Target is a action, thriller film directed by Sheldon Lettich.
A soldier now a mercenary, has been brought to a foreign country by a former
associate to aid in the security of that country's president.
But it appears that he's been set up as the man to take
the fall for the president's assassination.
He escapes and joins the rebels to clear his name and to expose the
true person behind the president's assassination.
David Benson, played by Daniel Bernhardt.
Colonel Shakwell, played by Robert Englund.
Major Oxnard, played by Brian Thompson.
Isabela Santiago Casillas, played by Julieta Rosen.
President Casillas, played by Mario Iván Martínez.
Miguel Ramirez, played by Jim Pirri.
Perfect Target is a 1997 Mexican-American action/thriller film
directed by Sheldon Lettich and starring Daniel Bernhardt.
The tone is intense.